digitaleditor.com 2007-06-27

# Statement of Privacy

|  |    
|  |  |  | 

Last updated October 2004

Simply put: We promise never to share your information with anyone unless we have to. 

Digital Editor is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Digital Editor Statement of Privacy applies to Digital Editor's family of Web sites and governs data collection and usage at all Digital Editor sites and services. Please read the Digital Editor Statement of Privacy below and also any supplementary information at the end of this statement for additional details about particular Digital Editor sites and services that you may use.

Digital Editor is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.

## Collection of your Personal Information

At some sites, Digital Editor collects personal information, such as your email address and name. At other sites, Digital Editor collects anonymous demographic information, that is not unique to you,such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. Some sites collect a combination of the two types of information. In some cases,information collected by Digital Editor may be combined with information obtained from other Digital Editor services and other companies.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Digital Editor and may be shared with other Web sites within the Digital Editor family of web sites. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Digital Editor for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Digital Editor.

Digital Editor uses encryption technology to provide registration and sign-in services. All of the registration information you provide will be stored by Digital Editor on our servers.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information through Digital Editor Discussion forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Digital Editor may read all email sent through our web site such as your Digital Editor Tell a friend or Contact the author emails.

Digital Editor encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Digital Editor so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Digital Editor is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Digital Editor family of Web sites.

## Use of your Personal Information

Digital Editor and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to operate Digital Editor and deliver the services you have requested. Digital Editor also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Digital Editor and its affiliates. Digital Editor may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Digital Editor does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Digital Editor keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Digital Editor, in order to determine what Digital Editor sites and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Digital Editor to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Digital Editor may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Digital Editor or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Digital Editor, including its Digital Editor family of Web sites; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Digital Editor, its web sites, or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Digital Editor or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Digital Editor abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

## Control your Personal Information

Digital Editor allows you to modify the information we hold about you by visiting your membership profile page. Please [contact us](http://www.digitaleditor.com/contact.aspx) if you wish to delete your membership account.

You may stop the delivery of future email from Digital Editor by following the specific instructions in the email you receive. The instructions explain how to stop receiving such emails.

There are occasions when you will receive emails informing you of technical service issues, product surveys, new feature announcements and news about Digital Editor products and services. You may not be able to unsubscribe to these mailings.

## Security of your Personal Information

Digital Editor strictly protects the security of the personal information you provide. Digital Editor secures the personal information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted over the Internet, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Use of Cookies

Digital Editor uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize Digital Editor's pages, or register with Digital Editor sites or services, a cookie helps Digital Editor to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as member ID, email address, and so on. When you return to Digital Editor, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Digital Editor features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Digital Editor services or Web sites you visit. Read "[What's a cookie?](http://www.digitaleditor.com/whatsacookie)" for more information.

## Use of Third Party Ad Networks

Digital Editor does not use any third-party Advertising Networks.

## Enforcement of this Statement of Privacy

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact Digital Editor.

## Digital Editor Discussion Forums

While participating in chats, communities or other public forums, Digital Editor cautions you against giving out personal information (such as names and addresses, phone numbers, social security numbers, credit card numbers, and driver's license numbers) to strangers online, which they may use for illegal or harmful purposes.

## Digital Editor Newsletters and Watches

When you subscribe to an Digital Editor Newsletter or Watch a page, Digital Editor requests your email address. Digital Editor uses your email address to send you the newsletter(s) or watch(es) you have requested. Digital Editor does not share your email address with third parties except as required to deliver the service. Each Digital Editor newsletter or Watch you receive will have instructions on how to unsubscribe prominently mentioned in it.

## Changes to this Statement

Digital Editor will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. When Digital Editor posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of Digital Editor. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Digital Editor will use your personal information, Digital Editor will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Digital Editor encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Digital Editor is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Digital Editor welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Digital Editor has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Digital Editor by [email](http://www.digitaleditor.com/contact.aspx).

### This site looks much better in a browser that supports current web standards, but it is accessible to any browser. [ Download one now ](http://www.digitaleditor.com/eu.aspx?url=http://www.webstandards.org/upgrade/ "This link is to a third party web site which will open in a new window")

|  |  |  |    

|   
---  
  
Today, June 27th 

registery cleaner coupon, Performance Scan coupon, Improve your Windows XP computer's performance and stability, FREE Process Scan Coupon Code 

* * *

Yesterday, June 26th 

Onlineshoes.com hasover 60 brands, expert customer service and a deep selection of sizes and widths. 

* * *

Exclusive! Free Shipping on all orders! Last Call Sales! Up to Extra 75% off, Bag Bang! Save on the finest Designer Bags 

* * *

ICE.com offers beautiful, quality jewelry at everyday prices. Save on a wide selection of diamonds, pearls, gemstones and more. 

* * *

Find the best prices for thousands of cookware, kitchenware and houseware products Cooking.com coupon codes and promotional codes for great discounts 

* * *

Save 60% on Dining Certificates. Restaurant.com serves as the community matchmaker, introducing great restaurants to great people. 

* * *

Save money with our Smart Bargain Coupon Code, Promotional Code and Discount Code 

* * *

J & R Friday Sale! 

* * *

Disney Shopping's Semi-Annual Sale - Save up to 75%! 

* * *

Save 25% off select Dimension purchases over $999, Save 25% on SELECT Dimension™ desktop purchases $999 or more 

* * *

Last Monday, June 25th 

At TigerDirect.com, you'll choose from brand name computers—the industry's top names—at prices simply not possible anywhere else. 

* * *

Second Act offers customers great deals on brand name consumer electronics. All of our deals are of limited quantities. 

* * *

Office Depot - Taking Care of Business. Office Depot, Inc. Founded in 1986, is one of the world's largest sellers of office products 

* * *

Save up to 50% during the ½ Price Days Sale! Lamps Plus is the largest supplier of home lighting in the nation, with factory direct pricing. 

* * *

Time Life take the very best songs, the very best TV programs, and the very best entertainment products 

* * *

Save money with our Coupon codes, Promo codes and Discount Codes for Bare Necessities 

* * *

Save a bundle at Brylane Home with our Coupon Codes, Promo Codes and Discounts 

* * *

HP is the largest consumer IT company in the world. 

* * *

Save money using out eBags Coupon Code, eBags Promotional Code, and eBags Discount Code 

* * *

Get complete protection from the two most dangerous threats on the Internet -- spyware and viruses - in a single, easy-to-use solution. 

* * *

Buy.com is the Internet retailer of choice. With categories ranging from computer hardware to software, from electronics to cellular and more... 

* * *

Free Delivery on Orders over $50 OfficeMax offers an array of services and products. 

* * *

Last Sunday, June 24th 

Use our coupon to save money on ZIRH, the leader in men's skin care products. 

* * *

TurboTax Free Edition - number 1 trusted tax software. Get Turbo Tax promotion code coupon, also web promotion code 

* * *

Save money on everything you need for bath, blinds, shades, furniture, home decor, lighting and more with Coupon Codes and Promo Codes 

* * *

Best Buy Co., Inc is North America's number-one specialty retailer of consumer electronics, personal computers, entertainment software and appliances. 

* * *

Memorial 2-Day Sale: CompUSA provides computers, electronics, and accessories at huge savings! 

* * *

Web Only: Save up to 25% on select LCD Monitors, and up to 30% on select Projectors, up to 25% on select Notebooks and more... 

* * *

Buy 1 get 1 50% off on select Activision Titles, Save $30 on Nintendo DS Value Pack 149.97 and 38 more... 

* * *

Last Saturday, June 23rd 

Save 20% on KODAK Fashion Accessories, Save 25% on all 1GB, 1GB High Performance, and 2GB High Performance Memory Cards 

* * *

Save on fathead, fathead poster, fathead poster wall, fathead star war, fathead gordon jeff, fathead manning peyton and fathead nascar 

* * *

OnSale offers more options and lower prices for everything from digital cameras and iPods to computer systems and peripherals. 

* * *

Quicken/TurboTax Bundle Save $20! Save 20% on Quicken Deluxe, 17% on Quicken Basic, 20% on Quicken Premier, 36% on Quicken 2007 and Free Shipping 

* * *

10% off All adidas NBA Gear, Winter Sale and Spring Gear. adidas lives and breathes sport, creating high-performance footwear and apparel designed. 

* * *

Save money with these Cingular Wireless cell phone promotional code, Cingular Wireless phone coupon code and Cingular Wireless Prepaid 

* * *

Up to 50% off select Motorola Phones! Free Samsung u340 Camera Phone! New flavor available only online. Get the LG Pink Chocolate for Only $99.99 

* * *

Book a Hawaii trip, get a free night, Flight + 4 nights from $565, Florida trip save up to 25%, Mexico trip save up to 20%, Caribbean save up to 25%! 

* * *

Last Friday, June 22nd 

McAfee offers a proven combination of hardware, software, and services to protect homes, businesses and government agencies from all threats. 

* * *

Old Navy's mission is to offer affordable, fashionable clothing and accessories for adults, kids, baby, and Moms-to-be. 

* * *

Print Sale! Get 10 cent and Save five cents on 4x6 prints. Save 25% off select Kodak Gallery gift items. New Customers Get 20 Free Kodak Prints! 

* * *

The Bombay Company offers furnishings with elegant designs, warm colors and luxurious textures. 

* * *

American Eagle Outfitters is a leading retailer that designs, markets and sells its own brand of laidback, current clothing for 15 to 25 year-olds 

* * *

Save with our Macy's Coupon Code, Promotional Code, and Discount. Looking for Free Shipping? 

* * *

Dell coupons and coupon codes for computers from Dell. Save on discount desktop computers, laptops, notebooks, servers, and more... 

* * *

Linens 'n Things Free Shipping on LNT.com's Deal of the Day, $10 off $10 purchase 

* * *

Babies"R"Us kicks off the Baby Fair Sale with 28 Hot Deals. 

* * *

Pre-Spring Sale Save An Additional 5% Abt Electronics is the nation's leading independent retailer of quality consumer electronics and appliances. 

* * *

MacMall has more than 100,000 different products. Get our exclusive coupon and save 3% OFF all Anti virus/Security 

* * *

Last Thursday, June 21st 

Save money on the most recent coupon and promotional codes, discounts and bargains from New York & Company. 

* * *

Save up to 20% at La Redoute Shop for the season’s essential trends. From Downtown to Urban & Country. 

* * *

Save on all your Pool needs at In The Swim with our Coupon Codes, Promo Codes and Discount Codes 

* * *

Wednesday, June 20th 

Shutterfly is an online photo service designed to help you get photo-quality prints from your digital camera delivered right to your door. 

* * *

Orbitz offers a wide selection of low airfares, as well as deals on lodging, car rentals, cruises, vacation packages and other travel. 

* * *

Target is America’s second largest general merchandise retailer. With a mix of trend-right style, high quality, affordability and attractive stores 

* * *

Billion Dollar Jewelry Sale: Take an EXTRA 15% off! Save on Hot Looks for Prom: 20-30% off prom attire! 

* * *

Save with Aeropostale coupons. Find the latest Aeropostale coupon codes, Aeropostale discounts 

* * *

15% off on all purchases when using your using Kohl's Credit Card 

* * *

20% off Satellite A130 Notebooks and 6 Months Same As Cash, Free Ground Shipping 

* * *

Save up to 50% on diamond rings, up to 70% on diamond necklaces, up to 75% on bracelets, and up to 60% on diamond earrings 

* * *

Get Free Shipping on NCAA Jerseys and Apparel, Dick's Sporting Goods is a full-line sporting goods offering brand name sporting goods. 

* * *

The NASCAR.Com Superstore offers the broadest selection of officially licensed NASCAR/driver merchandise available on the internet. 

* * *

Save up to 20% off entire order. Smarthome offers homeowners and contractors the widest selection of affordable home products. 

* * *

Free shipping over $75, 20% off ALL Swim Wear, New for spring! Find your best dress at Alloy Denim starting at $29.50 

* * *

15% off Site Wide, $20 off PDF Converter Professional, 20% on Dragon NaturallySpeaking 9, and 10% on all Nuance Products!! 

* * *

Tuesday, June 19th 

One Step Ahead carries Baby Gate, Pool Safety, Crib Safety, Appliance Safety, Kitchen Safety, Drawer Locks, Cabinet Lock, Window Safety, and more... 

* * *
